Good thing
he showed up just now
I wish this happened
every time…
How can I get out
of tough spots?
Huh?
Cho-seon
During the war-torn era
She manipulated men
to do her will
She was a flower
among beasts
I don't want
a woman's position…
If it means escaping
this bullying
I shall
become Daemun High's
Cho-seon!
I'll draw his attention
and make the prey
come to me
Hey, Il-tak
You're looking
sexy today
Hey, Hyeong-ju
I'm really craving
a smoke today
Want to go
smoke together?
Uh, sure, I guess?
Why are you
acting so friendly?
You always
said no before
I just changed my mind
Oh, right
The homeroom teacher
wanted to see me
Sorry
but you go on ahead
Behind the school
Okay, then hurry up
I'll be there soon
All right
now it's your turn
I'm going to
manipulate you!
Hey, Hyeon-wu?
Thanks for
helping me out before
Want to go smoke with me?
No
F***
Now I
actually have to go
smoke alone
with that jerk!
Wear this
And don't get ash on it
Uh, thanks